Finding Aid for the Lisa See Papers LSC.0564
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Correspondence
  - PW [1 of 2], 1983-1985 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    Incoming correspondence primarily from editors, publishers and publicists relating to new position as correspondent for "Publishers Weekly". Also includes letter to Carolyn See from Beverly Fisher.
  - PW [2 of 2], 1983-1985 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    Incoming correspondence primarily from publishers and literary agents relating to new position as correspondent for, and columns published in, "Publishers Weekly".
  - Editing Correspondence/Flower Net, 1996-1998 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    Correspondence primarily between Lisa See and her literary agent, Sandra Dijkstra, and editors at HarperCollins, relating to "The Flower Net".
  - The Interior - editing, 1997-1999 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    Correspondence primarily between Lisa See and her literary agent, Sandra Dijkstra, and Carolyn Marino at HarperCollins relating to "The Interior".
  - OGM - opera/Autry letters & cards, 2000-2001 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    Incoming correspondence, most of which mention "On Gold Mountain" book, opera, and exhibition.
  - OGM - Paperback Notes, 1996 (Box 37, Folder 4)
    Incoming correspondence relating to "On Gold Mountain".
  - WEBSITE FANMAIL, 1999-2001 (Box 37, Folder 5)
    Electronic mail received through personal Web site.
  - The Interior - letters [1 of 3], 1999-2000 (Box 37, Folder 6)
    Incoming correspondence, most of which mention "The Interior" and "On Gold Mountain".
  - The Interior - letters [2 of 3], 1999-2000 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - The Interior - letters [3 of 3], 1999-2000 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Mail - Misc., 1998-2001 (Box 38, Folder 2)
    General incoming correspondence, with some mentioning the On Gold Mountain exhibit at the Autry Museum of Western Heritage.
  - Correspondence, undated (Box 81, Folder 3)
  - Vintage correspondence, 1998 January 29 (Box 81, Folder 4)
    A letter from See regarding speaking engagements.
  - The Interior - music permission, 1999 (Box 81, Folder 5)
  - Kiriyama Prize information, 1999 (Box 81, Folder 6)
    See served as a judge for the 1999 Kiriyama Pacific Rim Book Prize.
  - Invitations, 2001 (Box 81, Folder 7)
  - Corrections Department correspondence, 2001-2003 (Box 81, Folder 8)
    Three packets from the Orange County Corrections Department in Florida. The packets include photos and student work on Flower Net, The Interior, Dragon Bones, and Making a Literary Life.
  - On Gold Mountain Correspondence, Circa 2001-2004 (Box 81, Folder 9-10, Box 82, Folder 1)
    Includes fan mail and correspondence regarding visits, the exhibit, immigration stories, and other authors' works.
  - Website fan mail, 2001-2004 (Box 82, Folder 2)
    Includes personal, publishing, and speaking engagement correspondence.
  - Correspondence received, 2001-2002 (Box 82, Folder 3)
  - Dragon Bones publisher correspondence, 2002 (Box 82, Folder 4)
  - Professional correspondence, 2002-2006, undated (Box 82, Folder 5)
    Correspondence regarding speaking engagements and publishing.
  - Publisher correspondence, 2003 (Box 82, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence received, 2003 (Box 82, Folder 7-8)
  - Correspondence, 2004 (Box 82, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, 2005 (Box 83, Folder 1-3, Box 82, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, 2006 (Box 83, Folder 4-5)
  - Fan emails, 2007 (Box 83, Folder 6)
  - Student papers (Box 83, Folder 7)
    This includes epistolary papers addressed to See for a linguistics course, as well as photographs and correspondence from a fan. More linguistics papers can be found in Box 84, Folder 6.
  - Correspondence, 2007 (Box 84, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 2008 (Box 84, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence from Mary Chetney's class, 2009 (Box 84, Folder 3)
  - Snow Flower and the Secret Fan: class essays, 2008-2009 (Box 84, Folder 4)
    Essays on Snow Flower and the Secret Fan from Jill Wendt's Sociology classes.
  - Correspondence, 2009-2010 (Box 84, Folder 5)
  - UCSB student work (Box 84, Folder 6)
    Correspondence from Roberta Gilman from the University of California, Santa Barbara. She encloses essays by her linguistics students. More linguistics essays can be found in Box 83, Folder 7.
- Publicity files
  See has been directly involved in the publicity for her books. These materials include itineraries, notes, and correspondence for tours. They also include cover proofs, posters, and other promotional materials as well as writings about Lisa See and her books.
  - Publicity: Lotus Land (Box 42, Folder 6, Box 43, Folder 8, Box 2, Folder 5)
    Box 2 contains: Press kit folders containing press releases entitled "Advance Praise For Lotus Land" and "Lotus Land: A Novel as Rich as the City It Celebrates". Includes "Lotus Land: Possible Questions For Discussion".
    Box 42 contains: Clippings. A photograph of Lisa See receiving a commendation from the City of Los Angeles.
    Box 43 contains: Publication announcement for the book "Lotus Land".
  - Publicity- Lotus Land, 28 Jan 1983; 17 Jun 1983 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    Advertisement for Lotus Land in 28 Jan issue of "Publishers Weekly" (pp. 10- 11); in 17 June issue of "Publishers Weekly", under "Back to Press", is notice of the fourth printing of "Lotus Land" (p. 54).
  - On Gold Mountain - Miscellaneous, 1991-1995 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    Correspondence, publicity materials, advertisements, interview, etc., relating to the book On Gold Mountain.
  - On Gold Mountain - Design/Promo Advance Quotes, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    Brochures; book covers; advance quotes; advertisements in New York Times and unknown publication for book "On Gold Mountain".
  - Book Tour Promo, 1995-1996 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    Correspondence, promotional material and publication party invitations for the book "On Gold Mountain".
  - The Interior - pre-pub materials, 1999 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    Bookstore invitation; book jacket; letter from Ann Dalton-Knott at Random House; newspaper clipping mentioning "The Flower Net" being developed for a film; etc.
  - Interview - KCET Magazine, Jun 1988 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    Interview by Irene Oppenheim in KCET Magazine entitled "Literary Trio Monica Highland" (p. 62).
  - Interviews; Reviews, 1983-1989 (Box 42, Folder 5)
    Reviews and interviews in various publications relating to Lotus Land. Also includes outgoing correspondence; correspondence about appearances; article in Writers West on writing Lotus Land; Lotus Land excerpt in Messenger; appointment book.
  - Book- Greetings from So. Calif., 1988 (Box 42, Folder 7)
    Publicity packets for "Greetings from Southern California" which include a photograph of "Monica Highland"; description of "Greetings"; article by Lisa See entitled "Graphic Arts Center"; etc.
  - Interview; Review, 1983 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    Interview in "USA Today"; "Lotus Land" book review in "West Coast Review of Books".
  - Citations, 1983; 1984 (Box 43, Folder 2)
    In two issues of the "The Hollywood Reporter" (August 31, 1983; p. 22 and January 25, 1984; p. 35), Lisa See is mentioned as being one of the authors of "Lotus Land".
  - Review, 17 Jul 1988 (Box 43, Folder 4)
    Article about the book "Greetings From Southern California" in "Los Angeles Times Magazine" (p. 16).
  - Review, May 1983 (Box 43, Folder 6)
    Review of the book Lotus Land in Los Angeles magazine (p. 52).
  - Review, 1983 (Box 43, Folder 7)
    Article about the book Lotus Land in Loyola Marymount University's Vistas magazine (v. 6, no. 4) on p. 12. Certificates of commendation from the City of Los Angeles were presented to Monica Highland by Mayor Tom Bradley.
  - LOTUS LAND MCGRAW HILL, 1985-1986 (Box 48, Folder 6)
    Book catalogs (one in a foreign language); book covers; press release relating to "Lotus Land" being acquired by Warner Brothers Television; publishing agreement addendum; and a Spur Awards entry form. Also includes book reviews from various publications.
  - LOTUS LAND, 1982-1983 (Box 49, Folder 1)
    Correspondence, press kit, publicity photographs, royalty statement, and notes relating to "Lotus Land". Also includes book reviews from various publications.
  - SHANGHAI, 1984-1986 (Box 49, Folder 2)
    Correspondence, contractual agreements, advertisements, interview and appearance dates, and notes relating to "110 Shanghai Road". Also includes book reviews from various publications. "Lotus Land" is mentioned in some items.
  - Lotus Land Clips, 1982-1983 (Box 49, Folder 3)
    Correspondence, articles, advertisement, book cover and news release relating to "Lotus Land". Also includes writers conference brochures; other correspondence; L.A. Times article on "Street Art"; notes.
  - SHANGHAI, 1986 (Box 49, Folder 4)
    Articles and book reviews relating to "110 Shanghai Road". Also includes correspondence; press kits; photographs; etc., relating to "110 Shanghai Road" and L. A. Times Magazine article on "Greetings from Southern California".
  - Greetings From So. Cal. (PR), 1987-1988 (Box 49, Folder 5)
    Articles; correspondence with Graphic Arts Center Publishing Company and Connie Terry Publicity/P.R.; press kit.
  - Interview, 6 Aug 1986 (Box 54, Folder 4)
    Interview of "Monica Highland" relating to "110 Shanghai Road" in "The San Diego Union" dated August 6, 1986 (p. E-11).
  - Flower Net/Foreign Publicity, 1998-1999 (Box 57, Folder 3)
    International book reviews relating to "The Flower Net". Also includes advertisements; publicity material; and book covers.
  - Flower Net/Eng. Edition, 1997-1998 (Box 57, Folder 5)
    Book review clippings of "The Flower Net" from International Press-Cutting Bureau. Also includes advertisements; book catalog; correspondence; article by Lisa See.
  - Interviews; Reviews, 1995-1999 (Box 57, Folder 6)
    Book reviews of "The Flower Net" and interviews of Lisa See. Also includes publicity material for "The Flower Net" and "The Interior"; correspondence.
  - Review, Oct 1997 (Box 57, Folder 8)
    Article in Buzz entitled "The See Dynasty" (p. 104).
  - Los Angeles Times Magazine, 1988 (Box 84, Folder 7)
    Magazine includes press for Greetings From Southern California on page 16.
  - Press and visits, circa 1980s (Box 84, Folder 8)
  - Press kit: On Gold Mountain book, 1996 (Box 84, Folder 9)
  - On Gold Mountain foreign publicity (Box 84, Folder 10)
  - On Gold Mountain Vintage publicity (Box 84, Folder 11-12)
  - On Gold Mountain: United Kingdom (UK) (Box 84, Folder 13)
  - On Gold Mountain: paperback tour (Box 84, Folder 14)
  - On Gold Mountain: hardback book tour schedule (Box 84, Folder 15)
  - People Magazine, 1995 (Box 84, Folder 16)
  - On Gold Mountain press (Box 85, Folder 1-2)
  - Flower Net press kit and press, 1998 (Box 85, Folder 3-4)
  - Flower Net tour schedule (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - Flower Net addresses (Box 85, Folder 6)
  - Flower Net reviews (Box 85, Folder 7-9)
  - Tammy - Flower Net (Box 85, Folder 10)
    Tour schedules, information, and correspondence.
  - The Flower Net publicity (Box 86, Folder 1-2)
  - Flower Net paperback publicity (Box 86, Folder 3)
  - Book tour promotion: Flower Net (Box 86, Folder 4-5)
  - Bookstore copies (Box 86, Folder 6)
    Packets of reviews and bestseller lists featuring Flower Net.
  - Foreign publicity, 1996-1999 (Box 86, Folder 7)
  - Flower Net press kits, 1997 (Box 86, Folder 8)
  - The Interior: publicity and clippings (Box 86, Folder 9)
  - The Interior: press kit, 1999 (Box 86, Folder 10-11)
  - The Interior paperback (Box 86, Folder 12)
    Catalog with The Interior on the front cover and promotional cards for The Interior in paperback.
  - The Interior tour schedule, 1999-2000 (Box 86, Folder 13)
  - The Interior United Kingdom (UK) publicity (Box 87, Folder 1)
  - The Interior mail list (Box 87, Folder 2)
  - The Interior publicity plans United States, United Kingdom, etc (Box 87, Folder 3)
  - Flower Net and The Interior reprints (Box 87, Folder 4)
    Correspondence, quotations, and layout for covers and advertisements.
  - On Gold Mountain Opera press kit, 2000 (Box 87, Folder 5)
  - Dragon Bones Random House publicity (Box 87, Folder 6)
  - Dragon Bones United Kingdom (Box 87, Folder 7)
    Correspondence from publishers with book covers and a clipping.
  - Dragon Bones Tour materials (Box 87, Folder 8-9)
    Includes tour schedules, clippings, the book cover, and correspondence regarding planning the book tour.
  - New mystery jackets (Box 87, Folder 10)
    Book covers for Flower Net, The Interior, and Dragon Bones.
  - Snow Flower and the Secret Fan bestseller lists (Box 88, Folder 1, Box 87, Folder 11-12)
  - Snow Flower and the Secret Fan book tour materials, 2001-2005 (Box 88, Folder 2)
    Includes ideas for possible future publicity.
  - Snow Flower and the Secret Fan publicity, 2005 (Box 88, Folder 3)
    Clippings and invitations to events.
  - Snow Flower and the Secret Fan publicity and sales updates, 2005-2006 (Box 88, Folder 4-5)
  - Snow Flower and the Secret Fan publicity materials, 2004-2005, 2008 (Box 88, Folder 6)
    Includes foreign sales data, marketing ideas, clippings, design proofs, and a cover proof.
  - Snow Flower and the Secret Fan book club questions (Box 88, Folder 7)
  - Snow Flower and the Secret Fan paperback tour itineraries, 2006 (Box 88, Folder 8)
  - Peony in Love artwork, 2006 (Box 88, Folder 9)
    This includes several different cover proofs and advertising materials.
  - Peony in Love bestseller lists (Box 88, Folder 10)
    Also includes some bestseller lists for Snow Flower and the Secret Fan.
  - Tour schedules and appearances, 2007 (Box 88, Folder 11)
  - Peony in Love paperback publicity and press (Box 89, Folder 1-2)
  - Shanghai Girls interviews and advertisements (Box 89, Folder 3-4)
  - Shanghai Girls invitations (Box 89, Folder 5)
  - Shanghai Girls sales reports and marketing correspondence (Box 89, Folder 6)
  - International Association of Crime Writers mailing list (Box 89, Folder 7)
  - Book party guest lists, 1995, 1997 (Box 89, Folder 8)
  - Mailing lists and guest lists, 1987-1988, 1995, 1997, 2001 (Box 90, Folder 1-3)
  - Speaking engagement materials, 1999 (Box 90, Folder 4)
  - Speaking engagement materials, 2000 (Box 90, Folder 5)
  - Speaking engagement materials, 2001 (Box 90, Folder 6-7)
  - Speaking engagement materials, 2002 (Box 91, Folder 1)
  - Speaking engagement materials, 2003 (Box 91, Folder 2)
  - Speaking engagement materials, 2004 (Box 91, Folder 3)
  - Publicity materials, 2005 (Box 91, Folder 4-5)
  - Publicity and event materials, 2006 (Box 91, Folder 6-7)
  - Publicity and event materials, 2007 (Box 92, Folder 1, Box 91, Folder 8)
  - Publicity and event materials, 2008 (Box 92, Folder 2)
  - Publicity and event materials, 2009 (Box 92, Folder 3)
  - Dragon Bones publicity (Box 97, Folder 1)
    Includes a flyer, press release, and biography.
  - On Gold Mountain paperback flyer, 1996 (Box 97, Folder 2)
  - The Interior cover proofs, 1999 (Box 97, Folder 3)
    Proof of the UK book jacket for The Interior, along with a letter from Ann Dalton-Knott of Random House.
  - Publicity posters (Box 101, Box 102, Box 55)
    Box 55 contains posters promoting See's speaking engagements and books, including Peony in Love, Shanghai Girls, and others. Some are as large as four feet high. Box 101 includes a matted cover of 110 Shanghai Road; a foam board advertising See's scheduled events at American Library Association Annual; and a banner for Glendale Public Library's One Book, One Glendale program featuring Shanghai Girls. Box 102 contains a foam board advertising a visit to California State University Channel Islands and a foam board of the cover for Lotus Land.
- Research files
  This series includes research for articles and books and primarily consists of clippings.
  - Exhibition Catalog, 10 May-28 Jun 1987 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    From the New York Chinatown History Project: "Pear Garden in the West: America's Chinese Theater 1853-1983".
  - Newsletter, Summer 1998 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    Newsletter of the Friends of the Museum of Chinese American History.
  - Committee of 100, Apr 1997-May 1998 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    Correspondence, newsletters, and background paper on Committee of 100. Includes "Asian Update" publication from April 1997.
  - Chinatown Biz. Council, 12 May 2000-11 Sep 2000 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    Correspondence and newspaper articles relating to the Chinatown Business Council.
  - Winter Blossom Ball, 1990-2001 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    Program for Chinese American Debutante Guild's 1990 Winter Blossom Ball; photographs of 1991 Winter Blossom Ball from "AsiaWeek" and "714" magazines; card from Ruth Ding, founder of the Winter Blossom Ball.
  - Chinese-Americans, 8 Jun 1998-29 Sep 2000 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    Chinese Film Festival program; Oakland Museum brochure on Chinese and the Gold Rush; manuscripts recounting a Chinese immigrant's life in the United States; lyrics to Chinese songs; writings relating to "Chinese American Women of Los Angeles"; etc.
  - Artists- Date, Macdonald-Wright, 1-3 Mar 2000 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    Correspondence relating to work by artists Hideo Date and Stanton Macdonald-Wright; catalog and slides of paintings by Stanton Macdonald-Wright; photocopy of catalog with information on Hideo Date's work.
  - On Gold Mountain: Medi Update/Editors List, 1995 November - December (Box 10, Folder 6)
    "NCBPMA News" (pp. 5-8 only), consisting mainly of a list of book editors.
  - St. Martin's catalogs, May/Aug 1995 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    St. Martin's Press book catalog containing information about the book "On Gold Mountain" (p. 75).
  - American Pacific Pub, 1994-1995 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    Correspondence, itinerary, newsletters, etc., relating to a special report on "American Pacific Publishing" for "Publishers Weekly".
  - Notes from SF - Retrospect., 1991-1992 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    Correspondence, notes, surveys, etc., relating to California/Bay Area publishing.
  - How To Date, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    Essays by various people on topics "Ideal Date", "Worst Date", "My Noble Deed", etc.; booklet entitled "So You Don't Want To Be a Sex Object"; notes.
  - "Glamour", Apr 1986 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    April 1986 issue of "Glamour".
  - "Angeles", Feb 1991 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    Issue of "Angeles" magazine. On pages 98-99, items in the photograph are from F. Sui One, the store owned by members of Lisa See's family. Also in this issue is an article on Los Angeles' Chinatown.
  - "Publishers Weekly", 23 Mar 1992; 20 Apr 1992 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    "Publishers Group West Hits Stride; 1991 Sales Up 25%" (p. 12); "Ingram's PRI Joins Prima in New Marketing Venture" (p. 7).
  - Press kits, Brochures, Program, 1978-1979 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    Information kits and notes on the first L.A. Women's Marathon; program for the International Martial Arts festival; brochures from the Rape Treatment Center; news release, fact sheet, etc., for Sporting Times magazine; Nisei Week advertisements; etc.
  - ASJA Directory, 1981-1982 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    "1981-82 Directory American Society of Journalists and Authors: A Listing of Professional Free-Lance Writers".
  - Early research, 1988-1996 (Box 35, Folder 9)
    Articles, bibliographic citations, and Web site pages relating to China and the poison cantharidin.
  - PAM'S HERB STUFF (Box 35, Folder 10)
    Photocopies from publications relating to herbs. Also includes notes.
  - Sentencing on Hochman Case, 1995 (Box 35, Folder 11)
    Photocopy of United States District Court case for United States of America, Plaintiff, v. Zhongri Gao and Xianglu Jin, Defendants.
  - TRAFFIC USA Publication, May 1994 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    Publication from TRAFFIC USA entitled "Prescription for Extinction: Endangered Species and Patented Oriental Medicines in Trade", by Andrea L. Gaski and Kurt A. Johnson.
  - Bear Stuff via Hochman, 1993-1995 (Box 36, Folder 3-4)
    Report of investigation by the United States Customs Service of passengers arriving in Los Angeles International Airport from Shanghai, and found to be importing undeclared "oriental medicinal goods".
  - The Bear Facts, 1990-1996 (Box 36, Folder 5)
    National Fish & Wildlife Forensics Laboratory newsletter; articles relating to illegal trade in wildlife and endangered species; World Wildlife Fund publications catalog.
  - Asian Trade in Bears, 1991 (Box 36, Folder 6)
    WWF [World Wildlife Fund] report entitled "The Asian Trade in Bears and Bear Parts" by Judy A. Mills and Christopher Servheen. Also includes notes.
  - PW mailing lists - SCCBA, etc., 1981-1995; Thermal paper. (Box 38, Folder 3)
    Membership directories for bookseller associations in California; members lists for the Society of Children's Book Writers; board of directors list for the PEN Center USA and the NCBA; directories of Southern California publishers; etc.
  - BANTAM, 1986-1987 (Box 54, Folder 9)
    "Ed Young's Rowdy Roster Review"; "Ed Young's Bantam Review"; Bantam catalog; flier for Karen Brown's "Country Inn Guides To Europe"; Jack Smith column referring to "110 Shanghai Road"; photocopy of cover for "110 Shanghai Road".
  - Los Angeles Times Magazine, 24 Nov 1985 (Box 64, Folder 5)
    "Los Angeles Times Magazine" dated November 24, 1985.
  - Chinese articles (Box 92, Folder 4)
  - China rhetoric - clippings (Box 92, Folder 5)
  - Paul Moore materials, 1998 (Box 92, Folder 6)
    This includes two documents by the Association of the United States Army (AUSA). The first is a Background Brief from 1998 March titled "People's Republic of China." The second is a 1998 February issue of The Land Warfare Papers entitled "The People's Republic of China in Transition: An Assessment of the People's Liberation Army" by Edward B. Atkeson.
  - Clippings, 1998 (Box 92, Folder 7)
  - Clippings for the new book, 1995-1998 (Box 92, Folder 8)
  - Notes for new book (Box 93, Folder 1, Box 92, Folder 9)
  - China - The Interior notes, 1998 (Box 93, Folder 2)
  - Hong Kong and Chinese newspapers (Box 93, Folder 3)
  - Information for third book (Box 94, Folder 1, Box 93, Folder 4-5)
    Box 94, Folder 1 includes correspondence to her children.
  - Parachute children clippings (Box 94, Folder 2)
  - Hulan in Chinese (Box 94, Folder 3)
  - Hong Kong papers, 1998 Fall (Box 94, Folder 4)
  - Dragon Bones research articles (Box 94, Folder 5-6)
  - Three Gorges Yangtze River articles (Box 94, Folder 7-9, Box 95, Folder 1)
  - Three Wives Commentary (Box 95, Folder 2)
    A photocopy of the Three Wives Commentary in Chinese.
- Exhibition files
  These files related to the exhibits See curated for the Autry National Center and Chinese American Museum include visitor comments, insurance appraisals of borrowed objects, planning notes, correspondence, and fundraising materials. In addition, files related to See's work at the Pacific Asia Museum are included.
  - Exhibition- On Gold Mountain, 28 Dec 1998-28 May 1999 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    Letters, facsimiles, memoranda, etc., relating to the "On Gold Mountain" exhibition at the Autry Museum of Western Heritage.
  - Exhibit materials, 16 Nov 1995-25 Jan 1999 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    Letters, facsimiles, memoranda, etc., relating to "On Gold Mountain" exhibition at the Autry Museum of Western Heritage.
  - NEH Proposal materials, 28 Dec 1998-1 Feb 1999 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    Letters, facsimiles, memoranda, etc., relating to the "On Gold Mountain" exhibition at the Autry Museum of Western Heritage. Includes material on the National Endowment for the Humanities grant.
  - Walk-Through with Object Lists, 30 Nov 1998 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    Object list for walk-through of the On Gold Mountain exhibition at the Autry Museum of Western Heritage.
  - Object Lender List, circa 1998 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    Object Source list and Object Lender list for the On Gold Mountain exhibition at the Autry Museum of Western Heritage.
  - Exhibition- On Gold Mountain, 9 May 2000-19 Jun 2000 (Box 5, Folder 7)